Stephanie Lauziere

salauzie@gmail.com | 803.767.3886

Over the past three years, I made my start in the tech industry working for an event registration company that provides an all-encompassing range of registration solutions for events and conferences. I was able to gain experience in several areas but my main area of focus was software development for online and onsite registration. This role allowed me to work remotely and also gave me the opportunity to travel when I needed to provide support for large scale events. This has given me amazing opportunities and I am ready to continue my pursuit of learning and making a difference in the tech community.

WORK EXPERIENCE

ITN International - Software Developer
May 2015 – Present
Charleston, SC

- ♦ Managed and developed customized web deployments on several solo and assisted accounts using C#, ASP.NET, SQL, IIS, etc
- ♦ Rapidly and efficiently resolved issues and deployed solutions in a high intensity environment
- ♦ Worked in an agile development environment to meet extremely aggressive deadlines for clients in the events industry

Bottle Bracket - Software Developer/Consultant May 2015 – Present Charleston, SC

- ♦ Worked with other developers to redesign and refactor code mainly using Python and Google App Engine
- ◆ Served as one of three developers to support the company website
- ♦ Provided support during company transitions in various areas including integrations, hosting, and SSL certificates

Value Medical - Outside Pharmacy Sales Representative July 2013 – April 2014 Charleston, SC

- ♦ Managed a sales territory comprising several counties
- Developed a tracking system to meet sales goals and give supervisors actionable information
- ◆ Served as a liaison between doctors, nurses, patients, and Value Medical staff

EDUCATION

Strayer University - Master of Science in Information Systems April 2014 - June 2017

The Iron Yard - Ruby on Rails Engineering (Three-month Intensive Course)

January 2015 - March 2015

College of Charleston - Bachelor of Science in Exercise Science August 2008 - May 2012

SKILLS

- ◆ Technical Skills C#, ASP.NET Web Forms, Ruby on Rails, Python, JavaScript, jQuery, AJAX, HTML, CSS, SQL, GitHub, TFS, Heroku, IIS, AWS, Authorize.net API, Stripe API, Google App Engine, EventBrite API
- ◆ Non-Technical Skills Leadership Roles, Interpersonal Skills, Microsoft Word, Microsoft Excel